<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
To change ttheir license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
To change ttheir template file, choose Tools | Templates
and open the template in the editor.
-->


<root>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that it is important that only those who are competent make decisions that are important.
        </content>
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            When offered a lot, they choses not to take so much of it. They thinks that for being comfortable, they does not need much.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that it is important to be persistent. When they is convinced of something, they thinks sticking to it is a good thing.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that only when they is disciplined, they will accomplish something in life. They thinks that it is important for them to maintain control over themself.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that having a goal in mind to work for is important. They thinks that it is honourable to have clear ambition in life.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that it is good to be open to change. Only if they is flexible, they thinks, will they be able to deal with life.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            Others are important to them. They thinks that it is good to help even if they does not get anything in return.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that it is important that things are done in the correct way. They believes, things work out only when done carefully, precise, and accurate.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            From time to time, it is important for them that people enjoy their lives. They can think of many things that make life comfortable.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            For them it is very important to live around people who look after each other. They believes that a strong community is crucial.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that it is unfair if people are treated differently, depending on certain attributes they have. People should have an equal chance to participate.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that it important that every group in society is proportionally represented. To them, fair decisions should only be made when everyone has an equal saying in it.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They is convinced that it is good to help each other out. They believes that people should support each other more.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            It is important to them to have strong leadership. They thinks that complicated decisions should be made by those in charge.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They believes that it is important to work hard in order to achieve things in life.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            It is important to them that in important decisions those that are affected have a say in it.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that it is okay to make mistakes. They thinks that people should learn to accept other people’s or their own shortcomings.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            It is important for them that things are being planned carefully. They believes that it a good plan is essential to most things.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            For them, life is about self-realization. They believes that it is important to do the things in life that are interesting and that help themself to grow.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            They thinks that not everything needs a plan. For them it is important to sometimes be open to do things spontaneously.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>
    <item>
        <content>
            In their view, tradition can help people to orient themselves and give them stability. They therefore believes that tradition is very important.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item> 
    <item>
        <content>
            In their view, society should not be restrictive, and anyone should have the chance to stand up for themselves. They thinks that being independent is very important.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item> 
    <item>
        <content>
            In their view, society would work a lot better if people behaved responsible. It is important for them to think about the people around them.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>    
    <item>
        <content>
           They believes that the world is changing rapidly. They therefore thinks that willingness to change is essential. 
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item> 
    <item>
        <content>
            They believes that everyone in society should enjoy life more. For them it makes not much sense for a society to suppress the individual needs with social norms.
        </content>        
        <answer>
            0
        </answer>        
    </item>                                        
</root>
